I want a car.
Chicks dig the car.
This is why Superman works alone.
Do try and bring this one
back in one piece, sir!
Don't wait up, Al.
I'll cancel the pizzas.
Batman, a new villain has
commandeered the Gotham Museum.
He's frozen the antiquities wing.
He's turned
the security guards into ice.
He's calling himself, "Mr. Freeze."
Mr. Freeze.
- Stop!
- Drop your weapon!
Stop or we'll shoot!
The Iceman cometh.
Please, show some mercy.
Mercy?!
I'm afraid that my condition has
left me cold to your pleas of mercy.
In this universe
there's only one absolute.
Everything
freezes.
Hi, Freeze. I'm Batman.
You're not sending me to the cooler.
- Nice catch.
- You break it, you buy it.
Grab the gem! Kill the heroes!
Yes, kill them! Kill them! Yes!
Destroy everything!
It's the hockey team from hell.
You get the ice, I'll get the Iceman.
Ah.
Thanks.
Sweet.
I got mine. Where's yours?
What killed the dinosaurs?
The Ice Age!
Hit me, boys.
Thanks for playing.
I was hoping you'd drop in.
Oh, yes.
Watch the numbers,
for they are
the harbingers of your doom.
Can you feel it coming?
The icy cold of space.
At 30,000 feet,
your heart will freeze,
and beat no more.
After you're frozen, your icy tomb
will plummet back to Gotham.
Freeze, you're mad.
This capsule explodes,
it'll slaughter thousands.
Freeze well.
- Who invited you?
- I was hanging around.
I thought you'd stay in the museum,
round up some thugs.
How about, "Nice to see you.
Thanks for saving my life."
- A batbomb?
- We must blow this up
before it turns Gotham into a crater.
Now what, call a taxi?!
Watch the first step!
Surf's up!
Gotcha!
Cowabunga!
He's freezing the furnace!
- I got him.
- Robin, no!
Stay cool, Birdboy.
Can you be cold?
You have 11 minutes to thaw the bird.
Will you chase the villain
or save the boy?
Your emotions make you weak.
That's why this day is mine.
I'll kill you next time!
Did we get him?
Drats!
My experiment to mate the orchid
and the rattlesnake has failed again...
but I still have hope for
the animal-plant crossbreedings.
If I can only find
the right dose of venom
these plants will be able to
fight back, like animals.
I will have given flora
a chance against
the thoughtless ravages of man.
Personal note:
My work would proceed faster
if Dr. Woodrue didn't whisk
my venom samples
back to his mysterious
Gilgamesh Wing.
Why won't he let me in the lab?
What is he doing in there?
Ladies and gentlemen
of the un-United Nations...
and our mystery bidder...
may I present
Antonio Diego
serial murderer,
serving life in prison,
and sole surviving
volunteer.
And what a charmer he is.
By merely drilling three
concentric holes
directly into Antonio's
cranial cavity
I have created viaducts into
the most primitive part of his brain...
the limbic system.
And now I add
my Super-Soldier Serum
code-named "Venom"
to which I add
my very own recipe of steroids,
and toxins.
Plug him in.
Time to scream.
Genius!
Behold
the ideal killing machine!
I call this little number...
"Bane."
Bane of Humanity!
Imagine it.
Your own private army made up of
thousands of these super-soldiers.
Bidding begins at a mere
10 million!
Turbo!
Show off for Daddy.
Dr. Isley.
Welcome to my parlor.
What?
You monster!
How could you?!
Our original sponsor had
no stomach for military applications.
- He cut the funding for our work.
- Our work?
Without your research
I couldn't have come this far.
Join me.
- The two of us, entwined, side by side.
- Join you?
I have spent my life trying to
protect plants from extinction,
and now you corrupt my research...
into some maniacal scheme
for world domination?
When I get through
you won't be able to get a job
teaching high school chemistry.
Do you hear me?!
You psycho!
Well, I can respect your opinion.
Sadly, I'm not good at rejection.
I'm afraid you'll have to die.
Yes. Yes.
Let the poisons and toxins
burn a grave for you
deep into the earth
you love so much!
Bye-bye, dear!
Fellow maniacs...
bidding begins!
Gotham University Labs
security video, two years ago.
Dr. Victor Fries
two-time Olympic decathlete and
Nobel Prize winner for molecular biology.
After his wife contracted a rare disease,
Macgregor's Syndrome
he hoped to freeze her in a cryogenic
sleep until he could find a cure.
Now, here's where
everything goes north.
That's got to hurt.
That liquid is 50 below.
But he survived somehow.
The cryo-solution mutated his body.
- What happened to his wife?
- Nobody knows for sure.
She's presumed dead.
Fries needs
extreme cold to survive.
His cryo-suit uses diamond-enhanced
lasers to keep him at 0 degrees.
If it's ice the Iceman wants...
Alfred.
Coming, sir.
Yes, sir?
We need the Wayne diamonds.
We going to trap a snowman?
Absolutely, right after you spend
10 hours in the simulator, training.
I made a mistake. I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
You were reckless
and almost got killed.
I'm fine! See!
Me, here, alive!
How we supposed to work together
if you won't trust me?
How indeed?
He's overeager, he's impulsive.
I can't trust him not to get hurt.
Perhaps the truth is
you really don't trust anyone.
Don't tell me
you're on his side again.
Despite all your talents
you're still just
a novice in the ways of family.
Master Dick follows
the same star as you,
but gets there by his own course.
You must learn to trust him,
for that is the nature of family.
I trust you, Alfred.
But I shan't be here forever.
Good night, Master Bruce.
Good night, Alfred.
Oh, dear, Master Bruce.
Good gracious, what a tumble.
There's a brave boy.
Yes, sir. I am so pleased you won
the bidding, Your Supreme Ruthlessness.
We're making the final modifications
on Bane right now.
We'll have a flawless super-soldier
out to you tomorrow by overnight mail.
Dr. Isley?
- Pamela?
- Mm-hm.
You look great.
Especially for a dead woman.
Hello, Jason.
I think I've had a change of heart.
- Or quite literally...
- Me?
...the animal-plant toxins had
a rather unique effect on me.
They replaced my blood with aloe
my skin with chlorophyll,
and filled
my lips...
with venom.
Oh...
and, Jason, one other thing.
I probably should have
mentioned this earlier...
I'm...
poison.
Whoo.
It's a jungle in here.
I am Nature's arm...
her spirit...
her will!
Hell, I am Mother Nature.
And the time has come,
for plants to take back...
the world so rightfully ours...
because it's not nice...
to fool with Mother Nature.
Hmm. "Wayne Enterprises."
Coming, Bane, darling.
We've got a plane to catch.
I'm Mr. White Christmas
I'm Mr. Snow
I'm Mr. Icicle
I'm Mr. Ten Below
Sing! Sing!
Come on, sing!
Louder! Come on!
Sing, sing, sing! Come on!
He's Mr. White Christmas
Come on, louder!
He's Mr. Icicle
Freezy...
I'm feeling hot.
- I find that unlikely.
- Okay.
So my hair is brittle
and my skin is dry...
I'd weather blizzards to have you.
You're the most perfect man
I've ever known.
What do you say we heat things up?
My passion thaws
for my bride alone.
Talk about your cold shoulder.
Frosty!
Yeah, boss?
Ah. Energy.
Battling the Bat
exhausted my power.
But...
I was successful nevertheless.
Absolutely, boss.
One more giant diamond of this size...
and my freezing engine
will be complete.
I will freeze the city.
Then I will hold Gotham ransom.
Unless the city bows
to my demands
it's winter forever
in Gotham.
The city fathers
will have no choice,
but to give me the billions
I need to complete my research...
so I can find a cure.
Leave us.
Sure, boss.
We need quality time.
Soon we will be together
once more.
Soon.
Alfred.
I'll get it.
I must've dozed off.
My sincerest apologies.
No apology necessary.
It's the first time it's happened
in 30 years.
Please be looking for me.
Actually, I'm looking for
Alfred Pennyworth.
Uncle Alfred.
Uncle Alfred!
Oh, my dear.
Oh, my dear
what a most wonderful surprise.
How did you manage
to come here all the way from England?
My dear, you are so kind
to your old uncle.
Uncle?
Barbara is the daughter
of my dear sister Margaret.
Both my parents were killed
in a car accident five years ago.
Uncle Alfred's been supporting me
ever since.
- You have?
- Secrets, Al?
Secrets are a virtual prerequisite
in this house.
Don't you think, sir?
I'm on break from...
Oxbridge Academy,
Alfred's Alma mater.
The new computer sciences division.
- How'd you know?
- Says so on the patch on your sweater.
Oh.
- What is it? It's beautiful.
- You can say that again.
It's a competition racer.
- I've been fixing it up.
- Really?
- I'll show you how to ride it.
- You certainly will not!
Don't worry, Uncle Alfred.
I'm terrified of these things.
Barbara, I hope you'll stay with us.
Oh, I don't know.
All this luxury really isn't
my style, but...
yeah, I'd love to.
Then it's settled.
Oh, but, sir, we...
We do get so busy here.
Don't be silly.
After all, she's family.
Uncle Alfred?
I came to tuck you in.
You came to tuck me in?
That's quite a switch.
Yes. What're you working on?
I'm trying to find my brother,
your Uncle Wilfred.
He's first butler
to the Maharajah of Miranjapore.
But Miranjapore is a floating court.
It travels through India.
Oh, I remember Mom getting postcards.
So Wilfred can be
rather difficult to find.
Well, I don't suppose they have
fax machines on elephants.
I've been trying to reach him
with no success.
When one grows ancient,
one yearns for family.
I have the same picture of Mom
by my bed.
Peg?
My nickname for sweet Margaret.
It's good to see you again.
I've missed you.
As I have you.
Sleep well, child.
You sleep.
Go to bed.
Good morning, Gotham.
It's Gossip Gerty reporting to you
direct from the Gotham Observatory
where billionaire Bruce Wayne,
chairman of Wayne Enterprises
is about to make yet another
legendary contribution to the city.
Gotham Observatory, Bane.
And step on it.
Step.
My father told me, "To succeed,
we need only pick a star and follow it."
So Wayne Enterprises is donating
the world's most advanced telescope
to Gotham's
Observatory Restoration Project.
With any luck
this telescope will give
future generations
a chance to follow their own stars.
Brucy
is it true that this new telescope
can see around the globe?
Yes. If you'll watch these monitors
right here. Doctor Lee?
Satellites in orbit allow us to reflect
light from anywhere on the planet.
From here, we'll be able
to see the sky anywhere on Earth,
and through this
intricate network of satellites
reflect it back to our
very own Gotham City for observation.
Just don't point it at my bedroom.
Brucy, you
and the exquisite Julie Madison
have been going out forever.
Are you going to tie the knot?
Uh, marriage?
Uh, uh, marriage?
You want to give me a hand here?
Bruce and I are recklessly in love.
And that's most certainly
enough for us. For now.
If you will follow me,
I'll show you the central control grid.
You're a lot of help.
Miss, you need to stop.
Move, fascist bulldog!
- You need an appointment...
- No, I don't!
Miss, you're not authorized
to be up here.
She has no pass, sir.
Little overly protective,
but you won't hurt me, Miss...?
Dr. Pamela Isley.
Doctor
what can I do for you?
Actually, I already
work for you, or did.
Your arboreal preservation project
in South America.
We cut our funding.
There was a conflict of ideologies.
Dr. Woodrue was a lunatic.
I see you knew him.
Yes. That lab burnt down last week.
I'm glad you escaped.
I have here a proposal showing how
Wayne Enterprises can immediately
cease all actions
that toxify our environment.
Forget the stars,
look here at the earth
our mother, our womb.
She deserves your loyalty
and protection.
And yet, you spoil her lands...
poison her oceans,
blacken her skies!
You're killing her!
Your intentions are noble,
but no diesel fuel for heat
no coolants to preserve food
millions of people would die
of cold and hunger.
Acceptable losses
in the battle to save the planet.
People come first, Dr. Isley.
Mammals!
A day of reckoning is coming.
That's right.
The same plants and flowers
that saw you
crawl from the primordial soup
will reclaim this planet
and there will be no one to protect you!
You...
You must be new in town.
In Gotham City,
Batman and Robin protect us
even from plants and flowers.
Maybe you'd like to meet them.
Caped crusaders are
going to help us auction
a diamond to raise money
for our botanical gardens.
Just a few mammals doing what
we can for the world's plants.
Thank you all for coming.
Good day, doctor.
Batman and Robin...
militant arm
of the warm-blooded oppressors...
animal protectors of the status quo.
First
I'll rid myself of the fur
and feathered pests.
And then Gotham
will be mine,
for the greening.
Uh, excuse me, chief.
I got something here
you might want to see.
I hate when people talk
during the movie.
One more diamond, my love.
One more.
"Bruce Wayne. Diamonds."
Hmm.
Very nice.
Ladies and gentlemen
Gossip Gerty
of Good Morning Gotham and I...
welcome you to
the gem of the evening.
Our own Commissioner Gordon...
displaying the famed Heart of Isis,
on loan
from the collection of my
close personal friend, Bruce Wayne.
- Think Freeze will take the bait?
- He'll be here.
...to dance with one
of our fabulous flowers...
...the famed diamond
draped around her neck.
Let's start the bidding!
I'll give 10,000 for the orchid!
20,000 for the tiger lily!
And I bid
30,000 dollars
for the lovely magnolia!
Boys, please...
let's show some gusto!
Hi there.
And you are?
Poison
Poison Ivy.
Mmm.
Why not send junior home early?
I've got some wild oats to sow.
On the other hand...
youth does have its advantages.
Endurance, stamina.
Forget the geriatric bat.
Come, join me.
My garden needs tending.
I'll take it from here, pal.
Wouldn't you like the earrings too?
Some lucky boy's
about to hit the honey pot.
I'll include an evening of my company
for the winner.
I'll bring everything you see here...
plus everything you don't.
I bid 50,000 dollars for Poison Ivy!
100,000!
And I'll bid...
500,000 dollars!
One million dollars.
- Two million.
- You don't have it. Three million.
I'll borrow it from you. Four.
- Five million.
- That's a utility belt, not a money belt.
- Six million.
- Seven million.
Never leave the cave without it.
You boys aren't going to start
fighting over little me, now, are you?
All right, everyone! Chill.
Chill. Chill.
Get the gun!
Yeah.
Boo.
Look at you!
Let me guess.
Plant Girl?
Vine Lady?
Hand over the diamond, Garden Gal,
or I'll turn you into mulch.
Pheromone dust...
designed to heat a man's blood.
Doesn't work on the cold-hearted.
If you please!
If you insist.
Clever little clover.
Whoa!
That's my exit cue.
Thanks.
Good night.
Cool party!
Commissioner, you have 11 minutes
to thaw these people.
Miss Ivy, you've just met
one of the most sinister men in Gotham.
That's not a man
that is a god.
Enough monkey business.
We've got work to do.
Monkey work.
- Pull back. You can't make the jump.
- I can make it!
- Pull back!
Redbird control codes.
Disable engine.
No! Don't do this to me!
No!
We won't make it!
It's a cold town.
Uh-oh.
I could've made that jump.
You could've splattered your brains
on the building's side.
The Flying Graysons were a team.
We had to trust each person
to do his job.
That's what being partners is about.
Counting on someone
is the way to win.
Your head wasn't on the job.
It was on Poison Ivy.
Maybe she wanted me instead of you.
That's your idea of friendship?
It's your rules.
It's your way, or the highway.
It's Batman and Robin,
not Robin and Batman.
- I'm sick of it!
- Yes, it's my rules that keep us alive.
If you want to stay in this house,
on this team, you'll abide by them.
This is no partnership.
You're never going to trust me!
Dear brother Wilfred...
I have tried
every address I know for you.
I'm just praying this reaches you.
We have very little time.
Batman monopolized the evening news.
Huh. Yes.
Congratulations on your
apprehension of Mr. Freeze.
Thanks. Thank you.
Is there something wrong, sir?
Alfred...
am I pig-headed?
Is it...?
Is it always
my way or the highway?
Why, yes. Actually.
Death and chance stole your parents...
but rather than become a victim...
you have done everything
in your power to control the fates.
For what is Batman...
if not an effort to master the chaos
that sweeps our world?
An attempt to control...
death itself?
But I can't, can I?
None of us can.
Hey!
Hyah!
Sorry. Um, so sorry!
Teach you that at Oxbridge?
Just a few judo lessons.
You know, London's kind of rough.
I suppose you had
a minor in motorbikes also?
Couldn't resist.
It's just so beautiful.
I just took it out for a spin.
I'll clean it tomorrow.
All right? Sorry.
Um, sorry. Good night.
Drag him into the cold beam.
Welcome home, Frost Face.
You're the common cold,
and we are the cure.
Allow me to break the ice.
My name is Freeze.
Learn it well...
for it's the chilling sound
of your doom.
All right, Freezie, you
can't live outside the cold zone.
Look at him stew.
Get used to it.
You're going to be here a very long,
long time.
Sadly
you will not live to see it.
Oh, yes.
Batface and Birdbrain turned out
to be much more
resistant to my love dust
than expected.
No matter. Next time
I'll just give them a stronger dose.
They'll literally be dying for me.
Hmm. "Turkish baths."
This looks promising.
Hmm.
A fixer-upper.
But with a certain homey charm.
Ah. A minus!
Current tenants.
Hello, my little pretty, pretty, pretty.
Hello yourself.
You look good enough to eat.
That I am.
Come and get me, if you can.
With pleasure.
Let's redecorate.
I've always hankered
for something on the water.
What is this floor?
It took God seven days
to create Paradise.
Let's see if I can do better.
Good babies.
Grow for mommy.
Bane, darling...
I found a fellow
who strikes my fancy.
A cool customer, yes.
Icy demeanor...
no question.
But I detect a certain ruthless charm
I may be able to use
to my advantage.
Honey, clean up this mess.
We've got company coming.
Honey.
Company.
- Bruce...
- Hmm?
We've been going out
for over a year now, and...
Okay, here it goes.
I want to spend my life with you.
I'm not the marrying kind.
There are things about me
you wouldn't understand.
I know you're a dedicated bachelor.
You've had your wild nights.
"Wild" doesn't...
Doesn't quite cover it.
You'll make someone
a good husband one day...
but I can't wait forever.
Look, I don't want to pressure you.
Because if I do
you'll just shut down.
I know the way you are.
Think about it.
Just promise me you'll think about it.
Okay?
You don't have to answer now.
Just think it over.
Here's some food for thought.
Who's Ivy?
- What?
- You just called me "Ivy."
Who's Ivy?
I wish I knew.
Enhance detail, 14 to 19.
Who are you?
Gotcha!
Banker, how much coin to play?
Two and a half.
You're the chick who won
the tunnel run two nights ago!
That'd be me.
That was kid stuff, sweetheart.
Why don't you take your tricycle
and run home?
- Want a side bet?
- How much?
- How much you got?
All right, let's race! Come on!
Just make sure the guys
are ready at the end of the bridge.
You got it, Spike!
Go, go, go!
Watch your left!
Out of my way, losers!
Nice try, girlie! You're next!
Excuse me!
Look out, baby!
Not bad for a chick!
Now!
End of the line, sweetheart!
So this is where you hang out.
How long you been racing?
Since my parents died.
I guess all the speed and danger
helped take me out of myself.
Made the pain go away.
You wouldn't understand.
You'd be surprised.
Street racing isn't exactly
an acceptable major at Oxbridge,
so they kicked me out.
But I've already won the money I need
to do what I've always dreamed.
Don't say you want to join the circus.
Alfred has supported me my whole life
and I'm going to pay him back.
I'll take him away
from this dismal life of servitude.
What are you talking about?
Listen, this whole
master-servant thing
it's really ridiculous.
Alfred is a sweet, noble man,
and he's subjugated all his life
and dreams to someone else.
Alfred and Bruce are like family.
Paying someone
to prepare your meals
do laundry, clean dishes,
you call that family?
Alfred's happy.
Happy?
You honestly don't know, do you?
How he's hiding the pain all the time.
Alfred's sick.
Alfred's not sick.
He's dying.
Dying?
Why didn't he tell us?
You know Alfred,
he'd never say anything.
But I can tell.
I can't believe it.
I know.
Cellblock.
Icehead, you got a visitor.
Your sister is here to see you.
Sister?
Brother, dear...
I heard you were blue.
Don't mind us, ma'am.
You can speak freely.
I don't mind you at all.
Men
the most absurd of God's creatures.
We give you life...
and we can take it away
just as easily.
- Right!
- Whatever.
I really am to die for.
Impressive!
Well, I, my most
unabominable snowman...
have been impressed by you.
In fact
I propose a pairing.
Hmm.
I've come to set you free.
An enticing offer...
but what does the lady
want in return?
Let's cool it for now.
I've got someone I want you to meet.
His name is Bane.
A laundry service that delivers! Wow!
What are you,
about a 50, big and tall?
No, I always go a size smaller.
Makes me look slimmer.
I'm running on empty.
I need the diamonds.
I'll help you grab your rocks.
Bane, dear
an exit, please.
Reinforced steel.
Not good.
Always winterize your pipes.
While I get my diamonds,
you and meatloaf retrieve my wife.
- You never mentioned a wife!
- Come on.
I hope Mr. Bane can swim.
Alfred, are you well?
As well as can be expected, sir.
My friend, I know you're sick.
I can get you the best doctors.
I have seen the best doctors.
A gentleman does not discuss
his ailments. It is not civilized.
I hope that I have taught you
at least that much, Master Bruce.
Alfred...
have you ever
regretted your life working here?
Looking after heroes?
No, sir.
My only regret is that I was never
able to be out there with you.
Not all the heroes wear masks.
Freeze has escaped!
We got this off
the Arkham surveillance camera.
Poison Ivy.
Two nights ago
Gotham Airport, these two arrive
by charter from South America.
They put 10 security guards
in the hospital
left a businessman dead from
organic poisoning, stole his limousine.
This is definitely the same pair
that sprang Freeze.
- Commissioner Gordon.
- Excuse me, gentlemen.
Poison Ivy, why would
she help Freeze escape?
She's definitely evil.
She was all I could think about,
like I was in love, but...
I know, then the feeling vanished.
I can't believe
we fought over a bad guy.
Bad, yes. Guy, no.
Well, I'm totally over her.
Me too. Definitely.
- Great stems, though.
- Buds too.
Yeah, those are nice. Here we go.
It's Nora Fries.
She's still alive.
He adapted his freezing technology
to reverse the disease.
He even found a cure for the disease
in some stages.
There she is.
Get the diamonds.
I'll rescue your bride.
We'll meet back at my place.
No. In my weakened condition,
I'm no match for the bat and bird.
You leave those boys to me.
Go!
- Can he save her?
- Her case is too advanced.
But maybe someday
with more research...
Poison Ivy.
I hate uninvited guests.
My lungs!
My lungs are freezing!
Chilled to perfection.
No beauty.
Just the beast.
Hey, there, pretty birdie.
Give yourself up. If you surrender...
To you?
Polly want a kiss?
There's something about
an anatomically correct...
rubber suit
that puts fire in a girl's lips.
Why are all the gorgeous ones
homicidal maniacs? Is it me?
Enough sweet talk.
Oh, no.
First you'll tell me where Freeze is,
then you're going to jail.
I'm a lover, not a fighter.
That's why every Poison Ivy
Action Figure comes with him!
Try not to make a mess when you die.
Yes, yes.
Hold it right there!
Stop!
Living in the shadow
of the big, bad bat.
You don't need him.
You're the star.
I can see it now:
Your own big, bright signal in the sky.
Let me guide you.
Let me kiss you.
Stop! Don't kiss her.
The victim at the airport,
toxins introduced orally.
- What are you saying?
- Why does she want to kiss us?
- I bet her lips are poisoned.
- Poisoned kiss?
You have issues with women!
You can't stand that
she'd kiss me and not you.
Something would be mine, not yours.
Exit, Bane.
Exit!
Ivy's right. I don't need your help.
I'm going solo!
What happened?
How'd they get away?
I've never been good with competition.
Who needs a frigid wife anyway?
Make yourself right at home.
Where's my wife?
There was nothing I could do.
Batman deactivated her.
- She's dead.
- You lie!
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
Their bones will turn to ice!
Their blood will freeze in my hands!
Kill them, of course.
But why stop there?
Why should only
Batman and Robin die
while the society that created them
goes unpunished?
Yes!
If I must suffer
humanity will suffer with me!
I shall repay them for sentencing me
to a life without human comfort.
I will blanket the city
in endless winter!
First...
Gotham.
And then...
the world!
Just what I had in mind.
Everything dead on Earth except us.
A chance for
Mother Nature to start again.
Behold, the dawn of a new age.
My mutant plants have the strength
of the deadliest animals.
Once you have frozen mankind,
these babies will overrun the globe.
And we shall rule them.
For we will be
the only two people
left in the world.
Yes.
Adam...
and Evil.
Yes.
You distract the bat and bird
while I prepare
to freeze...
Gotham!
It's stage one
of Macgregor's Syndrome.
I'm sorry.
All we can do is
make him comfortable.
Thank you, doctor.
Macgregor's Syndrome is
what Fries' wife had.
Alfred's condition is
less severe. Fries' research said
he cured a case like it,
just didn't say how.
No one else is even close.
I'm late for the dedication,
then I go after Freeze and Ivy alone.
- Like hell you do.
- Don't push me right now.
Or what? No one can
capture Ivy but the big, bad bat?
Yeah, right.
You want her for yourself, don't you?
I want her so badly, I can taste it.
That's the whole point.
She's done something to us.
She has us fighting over her somehow.
I know she loves me and not you,
and it's driving you crazy.
That's why you
stopped us from kissing.
- You're not thinking straight.
- But I am.
For the first time in a long time.
I want a Robin signal
in the sky, all right?
I'm tired of living in your shadow.
All that ends now.
I'm sorry, Uncle.
I was too late.
You must...
You must do something for me.
Find my brother, Wilfred
your uncle, wherever he is
and give him this.
I have duties
that he must fulfill in my stead.
Only family can be trusted.
What is it?
It is a sacred trust of two good men...
whom I have the honor
of calling "sir."
Take it to Wilfred,
and I implore you...
never open it.
You look so like your mother.
Bonsoir, glamorous Gothamites.
Everyone who's anyone
has flocked to the Observatory,
and tonight's star-studded
dedication of the new telescope.
And here's the man
of the hour himself
Bruce Wayne.
Mr. Wayne, how about a statement?
Excuse me.
- Over here, Mr. Wayne.
- Bruce! Bruce!
Commissioner.
- How are you?
- Good.
- How are you? Good to see you, Bruce.
Young man.
Hello, Gerty. Lovely to see you again.
Thank you.
- Commissioner Gordon.
- Yes?
I've always wondered
where does
that big old batlight come from?
Why, it's
on top of Police Headquarters.
I'd just love to see it.
But you probably don't have access.
Why, dear lady...
I am the police commissioner.
I have the keys
right here in my pocket.
Would you like to see it?
Who are you, dear lady?
On second thought,
you're way too old for me.
No, I'm not.
Please...
come back.
What are you doing? Come on.
- Show me how the satellites work.
- Okay.
First, I will turn Gotham into
an icy graveyard
then I will pull Batman's heart
from his body,
and feel it freeze in my hands.
Revenge!
Quickly, Bane.
Quickly, now.
Let there be light.
Only family can be trusted?
Well...
I'm family.
Access denied.
Hey.
I spend my entire life
trying to beat back death.
Everything I've done,
everything I'm...
capable of doing...
But I can't save you.
There's no defeat in death
Master Bruce.
Victory comes in defending
what we know is right...
while we still live.
I love you, old man.
And I love you too.
Access denied.
This better be one hell of a secret.
Margaret.
Access denied.
Peg.
Access allowed.
The combined power of
the telescope's reflecting crystals
will complete my freezing engine.
Yes.
No matter what they tell you,
Mr. Bane
it is the size of
your gun that counts.
Gun.
Where are you going?
It's not a Batlight, it's a Robin signal.
Ivy's calling me.
She is Pamela Isley.
She must've stolen Gordon's keys.
- She changed the signal.
- She did it for me, for love.
She infected us with pheromones.
I'm under some kind of magic spell?
She wants to kill you.
You'd say anything to keep her
away from me.
To keep her for yourself.
You said being a team
means trusting your partner.
Sometimes counting on someone
else is the only way to win. Remember?
You weren't talking about partners,
but about being a family.
So I'm asking you
friend, partner, brother...
will you trust me now?
- All the crystals are in place.
- Thank you.
Hi!
Oh. I'm sorry about the door.
Is the party over?
Over.
Who is this nutball?
Bomb.
If revenge
is a dish best served cold...
then put on your Sunday finest.
It's time to feast!
Tonight
hell freezes over.
Intruder alert.
Intruder alert. Identify.
Uncle Alfred, it's me. Barbara.
I expected you might find
your way down here, child.
I programmed my brain algorithms
into the batcomputer,
and created a virtual simulation.
I'd like to help Batman and Robin.
I anticipated you would,
and took the liberty
to create something in your size.
Suit me up, Uncle Alfred.
Hi there.
Is your thumb
the only part of you that's green?
You will just have to find out.
I want us to be together,
but you must be serious
about turning over a new leaf.
I need a sign...
How about "Slippery when wet."
...of trust.
Tell me your plan.
Kiss me and I'll tell you.
Tell me and I'll kiss you.
Freeze has taken the new telescope
and turned it into a giant freezing gun.
He's about to turn Gotham
into an ice cube.
I've got to stop him.
One kiss, my love.
For luck.
Bad luck, I'm afraid.
Time to die, little Robin.
I hate to disappoint you...
but rubber lips are immune to
your charms.
See you!
You're not the only one
who can set a trap, Venus.
Sorry, my vines have a crush on you.
Got to go.
So many people to kill,
so little time.
You're about to become compost.
Using feminine wiles to get what
you want? Trading on your looks?
Read a book. That passive-aggressive
number went out long ago.
Chicks like you
give women a bad name.
As I told Lady Fries
when I pulled her plug...
this is a one-woman show.
I don't think so.
Curses!
No!
Freeze is going to ice the city.
I know.
- And you are?
- Batgirl.
That's not P.C.
What about Batperson or Batwoman?
Bruce, it's me, Barbara.
I found the batcave.
We must change the locks.
- She knows who we are.
- We must kill her.
Yep. We'll kill her later.
We have work to do.
Let's kick some ice.
Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
We have less than 11 minutes
to thaw the city.
Gotcha!
Now!
Shield.
I'll finish off the city.
You kill the kids,
- but leave me the bat.
- Bat!
No sign of the snowman.
Maybe he melted.
No, he's just hibernating.
These heaters will thaw them.
I hope you've got
10 million more of those.
Eight minutes
and they're ice cubes forever.
Sunlight could reverse
the freezing process.
- Sunrise isn't for five hours.
- Here.
It's morning in the Congo.
- We'll relay sunlight...
- From below the equator...
It'll take the satellites
a minute to realign, but...
- Damn.
- Damn? Damn's not good.
Those targeting mirrors are frozen.
The beam won't work.
You thaw the mirrors.
Tonight's forecast:
A freeze is coming.
Bye-bye.
I got you!
No. I got you.
Yes.
It's one of those days!
Yes!
- Yeah!
- Yes.
Dirty fighter, dirty fighter!
The tube.
Yay, Batman!
Oh, no.
Hey, Freeze. The heat is on.
- You all right down there?
- Yeah.
Here goes.
Hang on.
Batman, you're doing it!
You've lost, Freeze.
I think not.
Bombs away, Batman.
Freeze in hell, Batman!
- What should we do now?
- Pray.
Hang on!
Grab onto my belt!
- Thank you, Batman!
- Thank you!
Need a ride?
- Most of Gotham's still frozen.
- It's midnight.
Telescope's gone.
There's no way to thaw the city.
The satellites could do it,
but it'd take a computer genius.
I'm on it.
No, I'm on it.
Have to do it upside down.
Men! Everything the hard way.
You're pretty good at this, little girl.
Well, watch and learn, little boy.
Looks like it's gonna be a beautiful day.
I'm taking you back
to Arkham Asylum.
Go on.
Kill me too.
Just as you killed my wife.
I didn't kill your wife.
As I told Lady Fries
when I pulled her plug...
this is a one-woman show.
But she's not dead.
We found her, restored her.
She's still frozen alive
waiting for you to find a cure.
She lives?
- Yes.
- She lives.
But vengeance isn't power.
Anyone can take a life.
But to give life...
that's true power.
A power you once had.
She's alive.
So I'm asking you.
Victor Fries...
help me save another life.
Show me how to cure
Macgregor's Syndrome, stage one.
And maybe you can also save the life
of the man your wife once loved.
He's still inside you, Victor.
Buried
deep beneath the snow.
Will you help me...
doctor?
Take two of these...
and call me in the morning.
I'll have your wife
moved to the lab at Arkham.
You'll be able to continue
your research there.
All we can do now is wait...
and hope.
He loves me.
He loves me not.
Not!
Surprise.
I'm your new cellmate.
And I've come
to make your life a living hell.
Prepare for a bitter harvest.
Winter has come at last.
Alfred.
Are you...?
Rather disappointed at how poorly
I have taught you proper housekeeping.
And quite well, it seems!
Thanks to you, son.
Thanks to you all.
Well done, Bruce.
You too. Well done.
I got one question.
When we fell off the telescope,
why didn't you try and save us?
It's the first time I fell
and you weren't there.
I figured you could handle it.
You know, sometimes counting on
somebody else is the only way to win.
Excuse me. I'm the one
who kicked Ivy's botanical butt.
Yeah, that was me.
I did it all by myself. That was me.
You are going back to school.
You'll never win this argument.
Partners?
Partners.
We're going to need a bigger cave.